I love the British band Oasis the group
was founded by two brothers No and Liam
Gallagher ha party brilliant and
obnoxious one time during recording
sessions no attack Liam with the cricket
bat they were like the Beatles but with
less meditation and walk cocaine and it
didn't take a meddling girlfriend to
break them up in 2009 after a huge fight
with his brother no quit the band and
started no Gallagher's high flying birds
now no Gallagher is one of my heroes I
bet we have loads of stuff in common
I like the party I'd love to quit my job
and I think my brother's a gay - I'm
pretty sure by the end of this we're
gonna be best friends
thank you know for being on the show
pleasure you're like my favorite person
in the world it was moving why are you
on my show why would you do this - well
the honest answer or the showbiz answer
I'll have the honest the honest answer
is I'm doing Jimmy Kimmel which is just
around the corner and I had a couple of
hours and I thought we'll throw this lot
of bomb scene as though he claims he
knows me I appreciate that
I sleep in Manchester I lived there for
two years do you miss Manchester yeah I
didn't miss it a little bit yeah I've
gotta say you talk about your
relationship with your father and that
you used to hit you and etc etc I don't
kill the living daylights out of me I
was hit by my mother but I don't think I
was hit enough because you're amazing I
was just hit a reasonable amount to be
good right right Michael Jackson was
amazing he got leathered he got 11 you
don't get Michael Jackson through
positive reinforcement things the best
thing that ever happened to me how's
your relationship with him now is it
I've seen him for what 20 odd years not
good do you miss erases I miss playing
the guitar I'm not being the front one I
miss that sometimes sometimes miss that
but I much prefer I'm not much much him
much prefer the vibe of what I do know
what keeps you going the way the world
is now if you've got it in you to put
out art then you should because there's
enough in the world as it isn't on
the internet and on YouTube and all that
that people like us we have to do more I
think people like us
happening no no I didn't start our own
what fans do you like now guitar bands a
shite these things so we're in this bar
in in Hollywood after after a gig when
this guy said excuse me
can he just cut my friends a really big
fan and he's like hey man it really
inspired me to play in all arts for a
sounds good I know what band you in he
said I mean the bass player in maroon 5
there in fact in
if you got the room 5 from what I'm
doing
you got out of my sight so we all pile
in these cars and go up to this party
about 4 o'clock in one hour coming out
of the toilet the bass player from
maroon 5 has stood there waiting to get
in the bathroom and I've have
are you still here and he went this is
my house I was like this great house in
my career I've been drunk on stage
several times I'm a little lit right now
I've been very open about my cocaine
taking know as you have both in lyrics
and in just talking about taking drugs
how are you going to tell your your two
sons and your daughter hey don't take
drugs the drugs are not dangerous it's
the people that take them out yeah you
got to be good at it but I was really
good idiots spoil it for the rest of you
just drive fast in a car it's all these
other just driving around me who are no
good yeah you got to slow down for them
you've got to accommodate them look I
think there's a lot of things they're a
lot more dangerous than drugs obviously
now in America we have all the problems
with guns and school shootings and stuff
like that more guns are not the answer
are they well statistically it's more
dangerous to be a school teacher in
America than me a cop in Britain so
saying the president doesn't help does
he say what we need those are the
teachers so what do you think of Trump I
was having him for the comedy value yeah
I like the mental image of him sitting
in bed on a Saturday evening in his
underpants
having a Twitter spot with the guy from
North Korea what is your opinion
lady or not but I think it's the biggest
waste of energy that's ever been landed
upon the human race I'm with you can you
tell the people at Comedy Central they
make me tweet every day for no apparent
reason only in squares social media
there is no cool people on it it's for
idiots yeah yeah it will have nothing
better to do than to sit around and you
know photograph food my son has more
photographs taken of him in a day then I
heard of my entire childhood be like
this is going great I mean we hate all
the same stuff but there's still one
thing I'm dying to ask one last question
I've been a lifelong fan and I know I
shouldn't be asking this but I'd kick
myself if I didn't ask do you like me
I've must say I've seen you pissed on
the telly yeah and I thought that's good
drinking lager just going through you
that was the best impersonation of me
and the other fellas
no smoking drinking I think you need
that's just like one of the Oasis
dressing rooms in the 90s we're not
gonna hang out are we No
[Music]
[Applause]